shad2前情回顧
我不是特別喜歡人
I don't like people very much.
我就不是那么和善的一個人
I'm just not a very nice person.
什么世道
The world is broken.
你不該在睡覺前看恐怖電影的
You shouldn't watch scary movies so close to bedtime.
可能福伊爾先生并不招人喜歡
We may dislike Mr Foyle.
但為他辯護并不需要喜歡他
We do not have to like him to defend him.
我才不是為了曝光度  瑪吉
I don't do things for exposure, Maggie
-那為什么接  -因為每個人都有權申辯
- Why do you do it? - Because everyone deserves a defence.
考慮到本案已經產生的新聞
Given the press this case has already generated,
福伊爾先生也得不到公正的審判
Mr Foyle cannot be given a fair trial.
我別無選擇  只能解散陪審團并釋放被告
I have no alternative but to discharge the jury and release the defendant.
威爾  好樣的  謝謝你  我的朋友
Will, good man. Thank you, my friend.
不客氣  保重
Pleasure. Take care.
我們在那兒等你好了  不過你抓緊點
Why don't we see you up there? But hurry up,
我有東西要給你看
I want to show you something.
凱特  杰米
Kate?! Jamie!
-爸爸  -杰米
- Dad! - Jamie!
-你替他辯護  -每個人都有權申辯
- You're defending him. - Everyone deserves a defence.
沒錯  瑪吉
That's right, Maggie.
沒錯
That's right.
媽媽  媽媽  爸爸
Mum! Mum! Dad!
救救我  爸爸  爸爸  不  爸爸
Help! Dad! Dad! No! DAD!!
-爸爸  不要  -好了  沒事了
- Dad!! No! - All right... All right...
好了  沒事了  乖  沒事了
It's all right, all right. It's OK.
沒事了  沒事了
It's all right, it's all right.
哈里斯  特雷弗·哈里斯  人呢
Harris? Trevor Harris. Anyone?
來研究威爾案子的控詞
Plea and case management on Will's case.
審判被提前了  我們要改日程
Whole thing just got moved up. We'll have to change the dates.
-好  -不  一點都不好
- Good. - No, not good at all.
該死的時間越多越好
We need all the bloody time we can get.
我們完全確定了  威爾的兒子什么也沒看見
We're absolutely sure Will's son didn't see anything.
我是說  如果我們有兩個證人的證詞
It's just if we had two witness statements. I mean,
就不用過于依靠DNA證據了
it would take the weight off the DNA.
-要是有DNA的話  -現在就這樣
- If it comes in. - This is where we are.
我們手上證據就這么多
This is what we've have to work with.
血液  目擊證人和不在場證明
Blood, ID, alibi.
如果老天幫忙  再加上點運氣
And God help us, a following wind.
不  你要聽我解釋
No, that's what I'm trying to explain to you.
聽著  我妻子不用須后水
Look, my wife does not wear aftershave
而我對彼得兔收藏品一丁點興趣都沒有
and I am not the least bit interested in Peter Rabbit collectibles.
所以如果要我幫你搞清楚來龍去脈
So if you want me to join the dots for you,
那肯定是有人盜竊了我妻子的身份
someone has stolen my wife's identity.
好吧  聽著  那是不可能的
Yeah, well, that's not going to happen, is it?
你沒法跟她說話
Well, you can't talk to her.
是  我已經去認過了
Yeah, I already identified her.
我走進太平間  還親了她的臉頰
I walked into the mortuary and kissed her face.
我嚇著你了吧
Did I scare you?
對不起
I'm sorry.
我也希望事情不是這樣  可惜事與愿違
I wish things could be different, but they're not.
聽著  如果你有什么話想跟我說
Look, if you ever want to tell me something, anything,
說說那天的事情  就來找我  好嗎
about what happened, I'll be here. OK?
直接說出來就行
Just come right out and say it.
我會聽著的
I'll be listening.
好嗎
Yeah?
下雨時  小動物會怎么樣
When it rains, what happens to all the little animals?
-你覺得它們會被淹死嗎  -福伊爾先生
- Do they drown, do you think? - Mr Foyle.
我曾經很喜歡下雨天
I used to love it when it rained.
但現在一下雨我就很傷心
But now I get so sad when it's wet out
因為我會想到那些小東西
cos all I can think about is all these little bodies
在泥水中掙扎呻吟
clawing and squeaking at the earth and the mud
在黑暗中淹死
and the water and drowning in the dark.
植物喝水可真沒良心  我知道它們必須喝水
It's a shame the plants have to drink. I know they do,
但依然是沒良心  一下雨我就很難過
but it's a shame. I get so sad when it's wet.
尤其是經過了這個夏天
Especially after the summer we had.
福伊爾先生  我們要確保你搞清楚了辯詞
Mr Foyle, we need to be sure that you understand your plea.
有證據證明我當晚在那間小屋嗎
Is there any evidence that puts me at the cottage?
有一個目擊證人看到了你  因而才指控你
You were charged on the basis of one eye witness identification.
一個
One.
對  一個  他兒子還什么都沒說
Yes, one. The son hasn't made a statement.
-暫時沒說  -暫時
- Not yet. - Yet.
你覺得他看到什么了嗎
You think he saw something?
只有一個目擊證人  這就是我們要面對的
There's only one witness. That's what we're dealing with.
那是什么
What's that?
茶
Tea.
-哪種茶  -我這種
- What kind of tea? - My tea.
我們還要談談你的不在場證明  莫里斯小姐
We also need to talk about your alibi, Ms Morris.
我們在辯詞中詳細陳述了
We go into considerable detail in our defence statement
當晚我們的行蹤
about our whereabouts that evening
我們相信莫里斯女士會支持這一證詞
and we are confident Ms. Morris will support this.
那為什么還要談這個
Then why do we need to discuss this?
就是要談
Because we need to discuss this.
伯頓先生是本案的唯一目擊者
Mr Burton is the only witness in this whole case.
所以他不能代表自己
So he can't act for himself.
-你很懂刑事訴訟程序  -我學過法律
- You're well-versed in criminal procedure. - I did a law course.
-是嗎  在哪兒學的  -劍橋
- Oh, really, where was that? - Cambridge.
安格利亞理工大學
Anglia Polytechnic University.
我們說不定在銀街擦肩過呢
We probably cycled past one another on Silver Street.
-世界很小  -確實
- It's a small world. - Indeed.
你說得對  伯頓先生不能以律師身份出庭
Yes, you're right, Mr Burton will not be in court.
他是目擊者  無論如何都不能代表檢方
As he's a witness, he cannot act for the Crown in any way.
話說回來  他老是壓在你頭上
It's just that, you know, he kept beating you, is all.
他不能出庭
He's not allowed to be there.
所以他只能看著
So he just has to watch.
我認為是的
I suppose so.
而且  當時很黑
Besides, it was very dark.
確實
Indeed.
真為那些動物感到遺憾  對吧
Shame about all those animals, isn't it?
你良心不安
You have qualms.
你說什么
I beg your pardon?
這是你辯護的第一宗大案  你熬夜工作
It's your first big defence. You're working late.
-卻良心不安  -他的妻子去世了
- You have qualms. - He lost his wife.
如果反過來  他一定不會猶豫
If the tables were turned, he would not hesitate.
就是這樣
This is how it works.
我只知道  如果我是威爾...
I just know that if I was Will...
但你不是他  對吧
But you're not him, are you?
暫時還成不了
Not yet, anyway.
怎么樣  我可能只能待五分鐘
All right? I've probably only got about five minutes.
-今早真是忙瘋了  -情況如何
- It's a bit of a crazy morning. - How's it looking?
我每次經過會議室
Every time I pass the conference room
都有一大隊人在敲門
there's a huge queue of people knocking on the door.
大家都想幫忙  伙計
Everyone wants to help, mate.
-誰是首席律師  -梅菲爾德先生
- Who's leading? - Mr Mayfield.
哈里斯先生是他的助理律師  其他人都很忙
Mr Harris is his junior. Everyone else was busy.
知道他們要靠哪些證據打官司嗎
Any idea what they are running with?
不想說的話就算了
You don't have to say a thing if you don't want to.
取證人員在花園里找到了一個12碼的鞋印
Forensics found a size 12 boot print in the garden.
但福伊爾的鞋子都是9碼  跟鞋印不匹配
But all Foyle's footwear is a size nine. No match on the tread.
就我所知  他們都還在等鑒證報告
So as far as I can tell they are all waiting for the forensics' report.
還有案發現場的血跡  以及你的指認
The crime scene blood. Plus, your ID of him.
-還有呢  -沒了
- And? - I think that's it.
他的不在場證明呢
What about his alibi?
他的鄰居說跟他一起吃晚餐
His neighbour said she had dinner with him.
他們還在尋找可能的突破點
They are looking into possible angles.
-他的鄰居叫什么  -艾琳·莫里斯
- What's this woman's name? - Eileen Morris.
再說一次
Say that again.
艾琳·莫里斯  對吧
Eileen Morris, right?
查了一下舊檔案
Did a little rooting around in the old case file.
只能查到這些
This is all I could come up with.
你還記得嗎  他喜歡養鳥
He's a bird fancier, if you remember.
看到是誰把獎杯頒給他的嗎
See who's presenting him with that trophy?
教區委員會活動組委會主席艾琳·莫里斯
"Parish Council Events Committee Co-Chair Eileen Morris".
恐怕只有這些給你了
That's all I've got for you I'm afraid.
不止這些  我肯定還在別處見過她的名字
There was something else. I'm sure I've seen her name somewhere else.
謝了  鮑勃
Thanks, Bob.
不客氣
You're welcome.
自助倉儲
福伊爾的不在場證明可能沒他們想的那么確鑿
Foyle's alibi might not be as solid as they're making out.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
真不公平
Doesn't seem fair.
這棟樓里最棒的法律頭腦
Biggest legal brain in the building,
卻不能跟他們談論自己的案子
can't even talk to them about your own bloody case.
是啊
No, I can't.
不能直接談
Not directly.
現在不是我給他辯護了  對吧
It's not like I am defending him anymore, is it?
你知道桑德拉·馬林斯一案的資料在哪兒嗎
Do you have any idea where the Sandra Mullins case files are?
知道  大盒子  我上周在研究那些東西呢
I think so, yeah. Big box. Stubbed my toe on it last week.
是不是就在我辦公室附近
Do you think it might be near my office?
可能吧
I think it could be.
shad2前四十名排行榜
shad2第一名
哈里斯先生
Mr Harris!
你看過科林伍德縱火案的案情摘要嗎
Did you see the Collingwood arson brief?
保密的那份
The private one?
看了  就在它閃電般飛向
Yes, I caught sight of it as it flew past me
某皇家律師的途中瞟了一眼
at high velocity on its way to one of the silks.
你怎么不從塔拉的本子里抽一張出來
Why don't you take a page out of Tara's book?
我已經夠抬不起頭了  謝了
My nose is brown enough already, thank you.
她做了必須做的事  你時不時的也可以做啊
She does what she has to. Why don't you do that now and then?
那我就跟塔拉一樣了  不是嗎
Because then I'd be like Tara, wouldn't I?
-你去哪兒  -福伊爾的辯詞要出來了
- You heading over? - Foyle's making his plea.
這么說已經開始了  情況如何  你怎么看
Right. So it's started. How's it looking, do you think?
沒有DNA  單個目擊證人  受壓指認
No sign of DNA at the scene, single eyewitness, recognition under duress.
回旋余地不是很大
Not a lot of wiggle room.
威爾的兒子在場  但如果他有看到什么
Will's boy was there... But if he had seen something, well,
早該說出來了  不是嗎
he would have said something, wouldn't he?
哈里斯先生
Mr Harris.
-別說  -不  我考慮過了
- Don't. - No, I've been thinking.
打住  我認真的
Well, stop. I mean it.
該走了
Time to go.
杰米你好  歡迎回來
Hi, Jamie, welcome back.
-你還好吧  -再見
- Are you OK? - See you.
-你沒事吧  -沒事
- Are you all right? - All right.
利亞姆·邁克爾·福伊爾  你被控告
Liam Michael Foyle, you are charged on this indictment
謀殺一人  你的辯詞
with one count of murder. How do you plead?
無罪
Not guilty.
法官閣下  鑒于證據缺乏
My Lord, given the lack of evidence
我方提出保釋申請
at this time we are serving a bail application notice.
我之前毫不知情  法官閣下
First I've heard of it, my lord.
我們遞交很及時
It was served in good time.
-我以為給你了  -我讀過
- I thought I gave it to you. - Well, I read it.
準予保釋  按相應程序制約
Bail granted, subject to conditions as per application.
謝謝法官閣下  我今早咨詢過排期員
Thank you, my lord. Also, I've spoken to the List Officer this morning,
被告知31號起有一周的時間可以開庭
who's informed me a slot is available for a week-long case on the 31st.
-很好  -等等  距現在只有幾周時間
- Very well. - Wait. That's only a few weeks away.
-我們幾乎沒有時間準備證據  -什么證據
- It hardly gives us any time to prepare the evidence? - What evidence?
福伊爾先生  你可以離開被告席了
Mr Foyle, you may leave the dock.
全體起立
All rise.
-還沒謝過你  -不客氣
- Never said thank you. - Oh, you're welcome.
-回頭見  -好
- See you soon. - Yes.
你惹大麻煩了
You're in a lot of trouble.
我給你做了酥皮點心
I made you some crumble.
我一定是忘了關籠子
I must have left my cage open
因為有只小小鳥剛給我辦了保釋
cos a little birdie just bailed me out.
你不該去的  艾琳  真的
You shouldn't have done that, Eileen, really.
只花了半個小時
It takes half an hour.
我說的不是這個
That's not what I am talking about.
拜托  我很樂意出錢
Oh, please. I was happy to pay.
歡迎回家
Welcome home.
蘋果的還是李子的
Apple or plum?
大黃的  就在教區委員會的冰箱里等著你
Rhubarb. It's in the fridge at the parish council, waiting for you.
它們不會等很久的  我保證
It won't be there too long, I promise.
-要做的事情還很多  -當然了
- Lots to be getting on with. - Oh, sure.
-我每天都喂食  照你交代的  -很好
- I fed them every day, just like you asked. - Good.
大家都餓了
Everybody's hungry.
好  我們再過一遍吧
All right, let's run it again, shall we?
驗尸報告顯示兇手動刀前勒過凱特
Post mortem indicates Kate was strangled before he cut into her.
-刀從...  -腳印有什么新發現
- The knife entered... - Any update onthe footprints?
現場到處都是  尺碼全都不對
Locus is littered with them, all the wrong size.
然后刀刃劃過氣管
After that, the blade passed through the trachea...
氣管是不能"劃過"的
You don't "pass through" The trachea.
是個鋸的動作  力氣非常大
It's a sawing motion. The core strength of a fast bowler.
-加文  -血濺得到處都是
- Gavin! - One hell of a blood spatter.
威爾來了
Will's here.
-到底是怎么搞的  -跟往常一樣啊
- How the hell did this happen? - The usual way.
怎么  他從正門進來的
What? He came in the front door.
我們看他妻子照片的時候把那該死的前門關了
Well, go and close the bloodly front when we view the pictures of his wife.
你要出現也該提前打個電話
You need to call ahead if you're going to just turn up.
我也在這里工作
I work here, too.
大家都支持你
Everyone's behind you on this,
但是如果你被發現試圖干涉此案
but you get caught trying to influence the case,
會危及到整個事務所
you're jeopardising the entire enterprise.
你是唯一的目擊證人  所以別插手了
You're the only witness. So hands off.
規則不一定要遵守
Protocol doesn't just need to be followed,
但是表面上一定要遵守
it needs to be seen to be followed.
我知道  我大學讀的法律
I know. I actually studied law in the university.
說句大實話
To be quite frank,
你連自己的辦公室都別去那是最好
we'd prefer it if you didn't even come into chambers.
如果再在家里憋上一天
If I have to stay home one more day,
我發誓我就要殺人了
I swear I'm going to kill somebody.
我需要工作  拜托了
I need to work. Please?
是今天  對吧  出辯詞
It was today, wasn't it? The plea?
他們沒給你打電話嗎  應該給你打電話的
They didn't call you? They should've called you.
-說呀  -無罪
- Talk to me! - Not guilty.
押在什么地方  斯科拉布斯
Remanded where? The Scrubs?
其實他被保釋了
Actually he got bail.
已拘留過  棄保潛逃的可能性低
Already in custody, low risk of absconding.
是有條件保釋
It's conditional.
-什么時候  -今天上午
- When was this? - This morning. Ohh!
你真的應該通過正當途徑來做這些事
You should really be doing this through the... proper channels.
-借我們口香糖  -是啊
- Lend us chewing gum. - Yeah.
-聽說福斯特博士的事了嗎  -聽說了
- Did you hear about Dr Foster? - Yeah.
我是威爾·伯頓  杰米的爸爸
It's Will Burton, Jamie's Dad.
告訴他我去接他好嗎
Tell him I'll be there to pick him up?
他跟阿爾菲走了  說要一起去搭巴士
"He left with Alfie, they said they were getting the bus together."
好吧  多謝
All right, thanks.
-康納  你見到杰米嗎  -沒有
- Connor, have you seen Jamie? - No.
-好的  -沒看到
- OK. - No, I haven't.
媽  有消息嗎  他在嗎
Mum, anything? Is he here?
他們說他已經走了
They said he'd already left.
你為什么不打電話給我
Why didn't you call me?!
帕特  杰米在嗎
Hi, Pat, is Jamie there?
我想問他有和阿爾菲一起嗎
I was wondering if he's with Alfie?
問過圖書館了嗎
Have you tried the library?
-新手機嗎  -最近剛買的
- Is that a new phone? - I got it recently.
聽聽看
Listen to this.
昨天在電臺里聽過
Yeah, I heard it on the radio yesterday.
-我要下車了  明天學校見  -再見
- Ah, it's my stop. See you at school. - See you.
他有跟阿爾菲一起下車嗎
Did he get off at Alfie's stop?
好  好的
OK. All right.
沒事  別著急  謝謝
No, don't worry. Don't worry. Thanks.
好了  我要報警了
That's it, I'm calling the police.
杰米
Jamie?!
-你到底去哪兒了  -我們去了商店
- Where the hell have you been?! - We went to the shop.
-有和陌生人說話嗎  -沒有
- Did you talk to anyone? - No.
你向我保證
You're going to promise me
以后不跟陌生人說話  好嗎
you'll not talk to anyone you don't know, all right?
不管是大街上還是游樂場  哪里都不行
Not on the street, not the playground, not anywhere.
以后我接你回家
I'm picking you up from school from now on.
好嗎  每天我都來接你
OK? Every single day. OK?
-爸爸  -讓我抱一會兒
- Dad! - Just give me a minute.
莫斯科的海獅在這個季節可饑渴了
The sea lions of Moscow are horny this time of the year.
-去你的  -放輕松嘛
- Up yours. - Oh, relax.
-走吧  我們到樓上去  -為什么
- Right, come on. Let's go upstairs. - Why?
走就是了  伙計
Come on, boy.
來吧
Come on.
就不能在公園見面嗎
Couldn't meet in a park?
人多的地方最隱蔽
It's the best place to hide, in a crowd.
-眾目睽睽之下  -狗屁
- In plain sight. - Plain stupid.
不就是兩個男人聊聊天嘛
We're just chatting. Two blokes having a chat.
你想怎樣
What do you want to do?
來聊聊足球吧
Let's talk football.
我曾經  現在也還愛著我們那支球隊
I used to love our team. I still love our team.
你知道我覺得問題在哪里嗎
Do you know what I think the problem is?
我們的明星前鋒不在了
We're missing our star striker.
他沒法上場  這是違反規則的
No way can he can play. It's against the rules.
坐在替補席上要他怎么得分
He can hardly score goals from the bench.
他想看比賽都不行
He can't even watch the match.
-他被禁止觀看比賽  -沒錯
- He's forbidden from watching the match. - Absolutely.
所以我有時候就想  說不定呢
So I am thinking that, from time to time, maybe
-我可以找人和你聊聊戰術打法  -丹尼
- I could get someone to talk to you about our attacking game. - Danny.
要是你不自在  門在那邊  我說的是門
The door's over there if you're feeling uncomfortable. Well, I say a door.
你要制定出更好的臨門策略
You need a better goal mouth strategy.
-老天  別這樣  -這怎么了
- Christ, don't do that. - What's the matter?
-怎么了  你說怎么了  -特雷弗
- What's the matter? What's the matter? - Trevor.
-你好  -這有什么
- Hi. - What's the matter?
你知道自己在做什么吧
You do know what it is you're doing,
知道我們在做什么吧
what we're doing, don't you?
-我們究竟在做什么呢  -聊天
- What is it we're doing exactly? - We're talking.
聊足球
About football.
-看嘛  男人聊足球  -沒什么不對的
- Here we are, men talking about football. - Nothing wrong with that.
區別在于  球員在比賽前聊足球
Except when footballers talk about football before a match
又不會丟掉飯碗  對吧
they don't lose their jobs, do they?
我知道這是不情之請
I know this is a big ask.
聽著  我明白
Look, I appreciate
你肯定希望梅菲爾德選別人
you must have been hoping that Mayfield would pick someone else,
選個更適合處理這種事的律師
someone more suited, perhaps, to something like this,
但事實上  大家都有工作在身
but the fact is, everyone else was gainfully employed and,
很遺憾只能是我了
well, I'm just sorry it had to be me.
-你是事務所最努力的律師  -我...
- You're the hardest-working barrister in the set. - Well, I...
謝謝  但是
Thank you. All the same,
-我要考慮考慮  -福伊爾有個儲物間
- I need to think about it. - Foyle had a storage unit.
桑德拉·馬林斯一案中他跟我們交代過
He told us about it during the Sandra Mullins trial.
謀殺案六個月前他將其清空并不再付費
He cleared it out and stop paying for it six months before the murder.
在訴訟過程當中沒有用到這一細節
It played no further part in the proceedings.
有人幫他接管了
Someone took it on after him.
一個叫艾琳·莫里斯的女人
Her name is Eileen Morris.
要是調查沒有進展
If something's not turning up it
就意味著你要換個角度入手
just might mean you need to look for it somewhere else.
證明推翻假定[拉丁文]
Probatio vincit praesumptionem.
-多謝你請客  -不客氣
- Thanks for the drink. - You're very welcome.
對了  這是給你的
That's for you, by the way.
-這是什么  -科林伍德案情摘要
- What's that? - Colinwood brief.
斯賓塞先生去休假了
Mr Spencer's off on holiday.
-他去哪兒  -我還沒決定好
- Where's he going? - I haven't decided yet.
bei1福伊爾  第15卷第133頁  艾琳·莫里斯
我要問你點事
I need to ask you something.
你在小屋里沒看到那個男人  對吧
In the cottage, you didn't actually see that man, did you?
太黑了
It was dark.
對不起  我不該問的
Sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
-什么事  -我打擾到你了嗎
- What? - Am I disturbing you?
你想干什么  彼得
What do you want, Peter?
能耽擱你一個小時嗎
Can you spare an hour tonight?
-現在太晚了  -你沒回答我的問題
- It's late. - You didn't answer the question.
今晚我抽不開身
Tonight's a bit difficult.
大家都很忙  親愛的
Difficult for all of us, my dear.
福伊爾是我們的委托人  他要求會面
Foyle is our client. He's called a meeting.
我們有責任參加
We have a duty to listen.
他聽起來很有興趣
He sounds very interested.
-好的  -說他想起來了什么
- Yeah. - Says he's remembered something.
我已經答應了
I said yes.
直接轉到語音信箱了
Straight to voicemail.
-找人去看下  -去哪兒
- Send a clerk round. - Where?
哈羅茲
Harrods.
他家  去他家
His house. To his house.
我們不能這么做
We can't do that.
我不會整晚都在這里待著
I'm not staying here all night.
你好  我是凱特  現在不方便接電話
Hi, it's Kate. I'm not here right now,
請留言  拜
but leave a message. Bye.
你好  我是凱特  現在不方便接電話
Hi, it's Kate. I'm not here right now,
請留言  拜
but leave a message. Bye.
你好  我是凱特  現在不方便接電話
Hi, it's Kate. I'm not here right now,
請留言  拜
but leave a message. Bye.
你好  我是凱特  現在不方便接電話
Hi, it's Kate. I'm not here right now,
請留言  拜
but leave a message. Bye.
-別怕  -別過來
- It's all right. - No!
是我  是我啊
It's me, it's me, it's me.
老天  你差點眼睛就瞎了
Jesus. You were half a second away from an eye patch.
桑德拉·馬林斯是福伊爾殺的
Foyle murdered Sandra Mullins.
你要知道這一點
You need to know that.
庭上你不是這樣說的
You said otherwise in court.
我看事情的角度變了
I see things differently now.
如果你對他有疑慮
If you had reservations about him
就應該對此采取行動
you should have acted on those.
他聲明自己無罪  而我為他辯護
He claimed his innocence and I spoke for him.
幫他擺脫指控  僅此而已
I lawyered him out of it, that's all.
但我知道是他殺了她  他是殺人犯
But I know he killed her. He is a murderer,
-我對此深信不疑  -這點我無法茍同
- there is no doubt in my mind. - We differ on this point.
我是認真的  你得小心點
I mean it. You need to be careful.
你真是見不得我事業順利啊  對嗎
You can't stand seeing me do well, can you?
-這案子對我有幫助  -對你有幫助
- This is good for me. - Good for you?
對你的遭遇我深感遺憾  但這是工作
I am truly sorry for what happened to you, but this is a job.
工作就是工作  僅此而已
Work is work. That's it.
福伊爾殺害了凱特
Foyle murdered Kate.
你接了那人的案子  你就危險了
You let that man in, you are risking everything.
不要重蹈我的覆轍
Don't make the same mistake.
晚安  威爾
Goodnight, Will.
說真的  千萬別落單
I mean it. Don't be alone.
加德納  你的...
Gardner! Did your...
朋友找到你了嗎
did your friend find you?
-朋友  -對  他按你家門鈴
- Friend? - Yeah, he rang your doorbell.
為什么你覺得他是我的朋友
What makes you think it was my friend?
他替你把垃圾倒了
He put your bin bag out.
她...
She...
出行的事由金來安排
King makes the travel arrangements...
全都是凱特的血
Blood was all Kate's.
沒找到與福伊爾匹配的DNA
No DNA match to Foyle whatsoever.
那還有別的線索嗎
What does that leave exactly?
事發現場威爾對福伊爾的指認
Will's ID of Foyle in the locus,
他的不在場證據  僅此而已
going for this alibi, and that's it.
你竟然還憑著這些成功立案了
Does that even get you through the door?
我們仍需整理一遍關鍵論點
All the same we need to collate some skeleton arguments
在辯方提出特恩布爾指引時  好將其駁倒
some on how to beat a Turnbull Direction should it come to it.
特恩布爾指引  有關目擊證人辨認的庭審條款
這就好像在隧道里跟地鐵爭論一樣
That's like arguing with a tube train in a tunnel.
我們還有別的選擇嗎
I don't see they have much choice.
沒有  確實如此
No, well, quite.
多謝你們的幫助  我們說過會支持他的
Yes, thank you for all your help. We said we'd be there for him.
-沒錯  我們會的  -具體怎么支持
- Yes, well we will be. - How, exactly?
我們可能忽略了一條線索
I think we've missed a trick.
我一直在翻查以前的檔案
I've been digging in the old files.
有一個儲物間
There was a storage unit.
是福伊爾在桑德拉·馬林斯被殺前租的
Foyle had one before the Sandra Mullins murder.
當時并未將它歸為證據
It didn't make it into the evidence
因為他在半年前就將其清空了
because he'd emptied it six months before.
然后交給了別人  猜猜接手的是誰
It was passed on to somebody else. Want to guess who?
她提供了不在場證明
She's his alibi.
在自己家里為他做了晚餐
She cooked him dinner at her home.
那好
Ok...
你確定儲物間是她租的嗎
You're sure she was paying for this?
從那時起就從銀行直接付款
Direct debit ever since.
我們沒找到跟案件有關的線索
If we're drawing a blank on the link to the locus
bei12010年1月到3月  利·福伊爾
2010年4月到12月  艾琳·莫里斯
不代表沒有線索
it doesn't mean there isn't one,
只能說明我們找錯了方向
it might just mean we're looking in the wrong place.
證明推翻假定[拉丁文]
Probatio vincit praesumptionem.
幫我給負責警官打個電話
Get a call into the OIC for me, will you?
我們要申請搜查令
We need a warrant in motion.
與此同時
In the meantime,
我們重新調查艾琳·莫里斯的所有情況
let's revisit all we know about Eileen Morris.
負責警官的電話
The IOC for you.
他終于發現
It's like he's finally worked out
怎么用自己的腦子了
how to switch on his brain.
怎么了
What is it?
他們又給我打電話了  問我證詞的事
They called me again, about my statement.
你不是給過了嗎
I thought you gave one?
他們要我再說一遍
They asked me to clarify it. Again.
-你怎么說的  -我告訴他們真相
- And what did you say? - Well, I told them the truth.
我告訴他們我們兩個當晚在一起
I told them all about our evening.
那不就行了
Well, there are you, then.
可他們為什么還要我說呢
But why did they need to check up on me like that?
我也不知道
I don't know.
不過沒什么好擔心的  不是嗎
But there's nothing more to worry about,... is there?
是的  應該沒什么問題
No, I suppose there's not.
你看起來凍壞了
You look freezing.
進屋坐一會兒吧
Why don't you come in for a minute?
-我得先回家一趟  -就現在
- Oh, I just have to pop home first. - Now,
沒問題吧
if that's OK.
好吧  好吧
Ok. Ok.
你會修水壺嗎
You know anything about kettles?
插頭沒插好
Oh, it's switched off at the wall.
這些人  這些律師
These people, these lawyers,
他們看不起你
they don't see you.
你知道嗎
Did you know that?
他們沒有一點憐憫之心
They don't have an ounce of mercy in them.
老實說  艾琳
And I'll be honest, Eileen.
他們很會操縱別人
They can be very manipulative.
艾琳  我想盡我所能保護你  真的
Eileen, I want to protect you as best as I can, I really do,
但是...
but...
我需要你對自己更肯定一點
I need you to be a little more sure of yourself.
-肯定  -對你自己
- Sure? - Of yourself.
我能做到  沒問題
Yeah, I think I can do that, yes.
你來扮演你自己  我來扮演他們
You be you... and I'll be them.
莫里斯女士  你能告訴法庭
Miss Morris, can you tell the court
十二月三日當晚你在哪里
where you were on the evening of the 3rd of December?
我在家里
I was at home.
你當晚吃了什么
And what did you have to eat?
-奶油培根意面  -錯
- Spaghetti carbonara. - Wrong.
-意式蘑菇燴飯  -錯
- Con funghi. - Wrong.
-不  不是  -不  不是
- No, it's not. - No, it's not.
我不...我不明白
I don't... I don't understand.
你的證言要有底氣
Have courage in your conviction.
別被他們嚇倒
Don't let them rattle you.
你當晚吃了什么
What did you have to eat?
意面...燴飯...
Spaghetti con... fu...
-我糊涂了  -是嗎  艾琳  你糊涂嗎
- I'm all confused now. - Are you, Eileen? Are you confused?
糊涂可幫不了我們
Confused doesn't help us.
糊涂只會把一切都搞砸
Confused makes everything go away.
我弄疼你了嗎
Am I hurting you?
是的
Yes.
我...弄疼...你了嗎
Am... I... hurting... you?
沒有
No.
你當天晚上做的晚餐是什么
And what did you make for dinner that night?
奶油培根意面
S... Spaghetti Carbonara...
來杯茶嗎
Cup of tea?
加文  我能問問您的專業意見嗎
Gavin, can I ask your expert opinion on something.
-當然  -出庭律師不能指導證人  對嗎
- Yes, of course. - A barrister can't coach a witness, correct?
這屬于嚴重違紀  會被立即撤換
Gross misconduct. He'd be out in a flash.
那如果是證人指導出庭律師呢
What about a witness coaching a barrister?
我有一個朋友
I have a friend who is displaying
他突然變得很能干
a sudden and surprising burst of talent.
我覺得他在獲取幫助
I think he's getting help.
那他不僅在拿自己的職業生涯冒險
Well, he's not just risking his own neck.
還在拿他的案子  他的委托人
He's risking his case, his client,
和他事務所的名譽冒險
and the reputation of his Chambers.
為了你的朋友著想
So, for the sake of your chum,
我建議你查清楚事情真相
I suggest you find out what's going on.
謝謝您
Thank you.
自助倉儲
你要看看另一個嗎  兩個都是我的
Did you need to go in the other one? They're both mine.
我們會查的
Yes, we will.
有點...抱歉  有點擠
Well, it's a bit of a, sorry, a bit of a squeeze.
這個也是我的
Cos this one's mine as well, so...
他們在儲物間發現了一雙12碼的靴子
They found a size 12 boot in the storage unit.
很有可能與案發地的腳印吻合
It's a strong candidate to match a tread in the locus.
福伊爾穿9碼的鞋
Foyle's a size nine.
但這不妨礙他穿大點的靴子
Of course it doesn't stop him wearing a bigger boot.
別管不在場證明了  仔細調查靴子
Forget the alibi, focus on the boot.
要她出庭作證  建立兩者之間的聯系
Get her on stand and make the connection.
但如果我們把她當作我們的證人
But if we call her as our witness
我們就不能盤問她的不在場證明  對吧
we can't cross examine her on the alibi, can we?
她的不在場證明基于她的良好信譽
Her alibi's based on good character.
很難直接戳破她的證詞
It's a hard sell to undermine her directly.
但如果你能利用儲物間的證據
But if you show in court
在法庭上證明他們有私下交往
they have an undisclosed connection through the storage unit,
她的證言就不攻自破了
you are undermining her credibility.
如果你能證明那雙靴子到過犯罪現場
You may not have to do any of that
那什么都不用做了
if you prove this boot was at the scene.
這是很重要的選擇  現在是艱難時刻
It's a big choice. It's bite the bullet time.
你應該往這方面去調查
That's the way you should go.
塔拉來了  快走
Tara's here. Walk away.
塔拉來了  快走啊
證明兩者的聯系  破壞證詞  一箭雙雕
Prove the link, undermine her. Double bubble.
還有  要確保搜查令可行
Oh, and make sure that warrant was kosher.
-特雷  怎么有點心不在焉  -塔拉
- Trev! Looking a little bit lost there. - Tara. Hi.
-你在這兒干什么  -丹尼也在這兒嗎
- What are you doing here? - Is Danny around?
怎么  你看見他了嗎
Why, have you seen him?
怎么樣
How bad?
她看見哈里斯了  可能也看見你了
She saw Harris. And she may have seen you too.
這下慘了  我們完了
So we're burned. We're done.
接下去怎么辦
So what happens now?
只能自求多福了
We cross our bloody fingers.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
-我做得有點過了  -沒錯
- I crossed a line. - Yes, you did.
我最近壓力太大了
I've been so stressed about everything.
我知道
I'm sure you are.
一會兒見
See you later.
今天是庭審的第一天
It's the first day of trial today.
他們會就證據展開辯論
They'll be arguing about evidence.
陪審團還沒來  你知道預審程序
Jury's not in yet. You remember the drill.
這周末我可能帶杰米去小屋
Probably going to take Jamie up to the cottage this weekend,
收拾下你的東西
go through your stuff.
我覺得是時候了  這樣對他也好  對吧
It's time. It might be good for him, you know?
教育孩子這方面我總是不如你
You were always better at that sort of stuff than me,
現在也只好走一步看一步了
but we'll see how it goes.
那邊的事都辦完了  我只等出庭作證
That way it's done before I have to take the stand.
所有人都盡力了  他們都很棒
Everyone's done what they can. Everyone's been great.
大家都很愛你
A lot of people really love you.
我們會盡力的  好嗎
We'll do our best, OK?
我保證
I promise.
放松  不就是找到個靴子  不打緊
Relax. So they found a boot. Big deal.
又不是DNA  我們不要松口
It's not DNA. We stick with what we agreed.
落實證據
Finalise the evidence.
艾琳會替你作證的對吧  福伊爾先生
Eileen will come through for us,... Mr Foyle?
我們一起吃的晚飯  她會宣誓作證
We had dinner together. She'll confirm that under oath.
-這么說靴子不要緊嗎  -在我看來是的
- So the boot's not a problem? - Not from where I'm sitting.
就剩他和他的證詞了
Just him and what he says he saw.
目前為止是這樣
As it stands. Yes.
目前為止
As it stands.
你確定你準備好了嗎
You sure you're up for this?
好
Right.
從這兒開始好嗎
Shall we start in here?
來  過來
Hey, come here.
沒事了  都過去了
It's all right. It's all right.
沒事了
It's OK.
-爸爸  -什么事
- Dad? - Yeah.
我能把書放到eBay上賣嗎
Can I sell my books on eBay?
你想怎么處理都行
You can do whatever you want with them.
我說不定也會這么做的
I might do the same myself.
你  用eBay
You? On eBay?
你對電腦一竅不通
You're rubbish with computers.
我就要  怎么著了
Yes. Me. What?
不可能  你做不到的
There's no way. No way.
你連怎么開機都不會
You can't even turn a computer on.
你要是做得到我把帽子吃下去
I mean, I would eat my hat.
我連帽子都沒有
And I don't even have a hat.
爸爸
Dad?
媽媽說這是意外之喜
Mum said it was a surprise.
好大一個驚喜
A nice surprise.
按5快速撥號  好嗎
Speed-dial five, would you, please?
發生什么事了
What's going on?
我要找人談談  然后再回來  好嗎
I need to speak to someone, then we'll come back, OK?
可以撥了嗎
Ready to dial?
-能現在就回去嗎  -按5  按住不動
- Can we go back now? - Press five on that phone and hold it down.
-喂  -你打算什么時候再告訴我
- Hello. - When were you planning on telling me?!
是威爾嗎
Will?
-等他進監獄了還是永遠不說  -聽我說
- When he was in jail? Never? - Listen...
還是打算把片子寄到我家來
Were you just going to send me an ultrasound in the post?
-你在開車嗎  -今晚我要和所有人見面
- Are you driving? - I want a meeting with everyone tonight.
你  加文  驗尸官  所有人
You, Gavin, the coroner. Everyone!
-掛掉  -聽我說
- Hang up. - Listen to me.
抱歉  杰米
Sorry, Jamie.
杰米
Jamie?
我應該更拼命地跟他打
I should have fought him harder.
都是我的錯  對不起
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
我不該放棄的
I should've tried again.
杰米  你在說什么
Jamie, what are you saying?
我抓傷了他的頭
I scratched his head.
你用手去抓他了
You scratched him with your hands?!
-然后我躲起來了  -你在門后的盒子里
- And then I hid. - You were in a box by the door.
最開始不在那兒
Not the first time.
-你挪過位置  -爸爸  小心
- You moved?! - Dad, look out!
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也是
Me too.
你做個深呼吸  好嗎
I just need you to take a nice deep breath, OK?
然后告訴我到底發生了什么
And now I want you to explain to me exactly what happened.
喂
Yep.
瑪吉  我是彼得
"Maggie, Peter.
法醫在小屋里找到了DNA
Forensic team just found DNA at the cottage."
福伊爾的DNA嗎
Foyle's?
嗯  那個男孩移動過
"Mmm. The boy moved,
他們在水槽底下提取到了樣本
they found a sample under the sink."
打電話叫瑪吉來
Get on the phone and get Maggie!
我要見我的法律團隊  不是你  希姆金斯
I want my legal team, not you, Simpkins!
你快要把我逼瘋了  我再也不想聽你說話了
You're driving me up the wall. I can't hear you speak anymore!
"是DNA  福伊爾先生  是DNA"
"DNA it is, Mr Foyle. It's DNA!"
DNA是什么意思  快讓瑪吉過來
What does DNA mean?! Get Maggie here now!
15層到了  準備開門
"15th Floor. Doors opening."
找到的DNA到底是什么DNA
What kind of DNA is the DNA that we've got?!
DNA是從哪兒提取的  希姆金斯先生
Where did this DNA come from, Mr Simpkins!
"我無法回答你  福伊爾先生"
"I can't tell you, Mr Foyle."
是頭發嗎  希姆金斯先生
Is it from hair, Mr Simpkins?
還是精液
Is it from semen?!
-你把他鎖起來了  -他說他只想和你談
- You've locked him in? - He said he'll only speak with you.
-你把他鎖起來了  -沒錯
- You've locked him in? - Correct.
我們之前在討論他的不在場證明
We were discussing his alibi.
然后談話轉向了新發現的DNA證據
Then the conversation drifted to the new DNA evidence.
然后你就不管了
And you let it?
只是少量的樣本
It's only a low sample.
如果我們處理得當
Manifestly unreliable
就能證明這個證據明顯不可靠
if we do our job properly.
-可他不會這么想  對嗎  -我想是的
- He's not going to see it that way, is he? - I suppose not.
它證明我在那兒
It puts me there.
你在擔心發現的DNA
You're concerned about the DNA.
它證明我在案發的小屋里
It puts me in that cottage.
它證明我"在案發現場"  瑪格麗特
It puts me "At the locus", Margaret.
現在他們認為我是兇手
And now they think it's me.
他們可能認為這證明你去過小屋
They might think it says you were in the cottage...
從現在開始要變成這樣子了  是吧
Is this how it's going to be? Here on in.
你以為我喜歡一輩子就坐在
Do you think I like spending my entire life
一間不通氣的屋子里聞他的咖啡味兒嗎
sitting in an airless room with his coffee breath?
簡直像是顆定時炸彈  活活耗死你
It's like an infernal machine. It chews you up.
不說話  也不聽
Doesn't speak. Doesn't listen.
就是滴答滴答往前走
Just keeps moving forward.
而你什么也做不了
There's nothing you can do!
好吧
Ok.
-我們需要做好準備  -我們
- We need to back up for moment. - We?
英國律師討論案情時不得提及客戶姓名  必須用第一人稱
我們有確鑿的不在場證明
We have a very clear alibi.
我們
We?
你喜歡用"我們"這個詞  是嗎
You love it, don't you. "We".
我們在同一條船上
We are one and the same.
從庭審的角度看
In terms of this trial,
我們的命運是交織在一起的
our fates are intertwined.
但是"我們"不會都去坐牢  對嗎
But "We" don't go to prison. Do we?
我們不在小屋里
We were not in the cottage.
對  我們不在
No,... we... weren't.
所以我們要弄清楚為何DNA說明的情況相反
So, we need to work out why the DNA would say that.
但這是科學  你不能和科學辯論
But it's science. And you can't argue with science.
我可以  福伊爾先生
I can, Mr Foyle.
事實上  我很有說服力
In fact, I can be very persuasive.
很好
Good.
請全體起立
Be upstanding in court.
伯頓先生  我知道這樣的狀況
Mr Burton, I know this is going to be hard for you
對你來說很痛苦
given the circumstances,
所以你可以慢慢來
so please take your time.
-我透過窗戶看到了他  -他是誰
- I saw him through the window. - Him being?
-利亞姆·福伊爾  -你認識他嗎
- Liam Foyle. - He was known to you?
認識  我剛在一次刑事審判中為他做過辯護
Yes. I'd just defended him in a criminal trial.
在此期間你多久見他一次
How often would you say you saw him during that period?
幾乎每天都見
Almost daily.
在整個庭審期間  六個月的時間
Over the trial period, six months.
那天在廚房窗戶外盯著你的人
Is there any doubt in your mind whatsoever
正是那次庭審期間你每天見的人
that the man you saw during thosetimes
你對此判斷
was the same man you saw
有沒有產生過任何的懷疑
staring at you through the kitchen window?
沒有任何懷疑
None whatsoever.
加德納女士
Ms Gardner?
伯頓先生  你是一名訓練有素的
Mr Burton, you are a practising
-刑事辯護律師  是嗎  -是
- criminal defence barrister, are you not? - Yes.
如果案件中對被告的控訴
If a situation arises where a case against an accused
主要依賴證人對被告的指認
depends to a great extent on the identification of the accused,
這種情況下法官應該警示陪審團嗎
is there a warning the judge should give the jury?
應該
Yes.
-這種警示的名稱是什么  -特恩布爾指引
- What is that warning called? -It's called a Turnbull Direction.
從你的專業角度看  一個案件
In your professional opinion, is it important for the judge
如此嚴重依賴目擊證人的指認
to warn the jury of the need for caution
在陪審團給出判決之前  法官的警示
before convicting anyone in any case that relies so heavily
-是否重要  -是
- on eyewitness identification? - Yes.
在此種情況中  法官閣下是否需要
Should the judge, in that situation,
請陪審團仔細調查
ask the jury to closely examine
證人指認時的環境因素
every circumstance in which the identification was made?
-是  我可以列出來  -是否...
- Yes. I can list them for you if you like. - Would...
不用  謝謝  我完全可以自己回想起來
No, thank you, I'm more than capable of recalling them on my own.
你發現她的尸體時  從窗戶里看到了誰
When you found her body, who did you see in the window?
我看見利亞姆·福伊爾
I saw Liam Foyle.
-你"確定"看見的是他  -是
- You had "No doubt whatsoever" It was him. - Yes.
凱特·伯頓被殺害時
There was a second individual present at the time
現場還有第二個人  是嗎
Kate Burton was killed, wasn't there?
伯頓先生
Mr Burton?
是
Yes.
-是你的兒子杰米  對嗎  -是
- This would be your son James, is that right? - Yes.
根據他的陳述
Well, according to his statement,
他不能
he was unable to make
"辨認出襲擊者的樣貌"  是嗎
"Any identification of the attacker whatsoever." Is that right?
他才九歲  當時躲在盒子里
He's nine years old. He was hiding in a box.
我再問一次
So if I might ask again.
你是否認為
Is it your understanding
他無法辨認出襲擊者
that he was not able to identify the attacker?
是
Yes.
因此現場有半數人
So 50 percent of persons present
無法明確辨認出襲擊者
were not able to give a positive identification of the attacker.
伯頓先生  陪審團在判決時
Mr Burton, when a jury convicts,
是否要排除一切懷疑
is it beyond all doubt?
是這樣規定的對嗎
Is... Is that the term?
-合理懷疑  -排除合理懷疑
- Reasonable doubt. - Beyond reasonable doubt.
讓我們思考一下本案中
Now let's have a think about what might be reasonable
存在的可能  好嗎
in this situation, shall we?
當你看見那個人時  你指稱就是被告
When you saw the man you are alleging was the accused,
-福伊爾先生  當時很黑嗎  -是的
- Mr Foyle, was it dark? - Yes.
-你當時有壓力嗎  -這算什么問題
- Were you under stress? - Is that a serious question?
-她懷孕了  你知道嗎  -伯頓先生
- She was pregnant, did you know that? - Mr Burton.
-法官閣下  -根據行為準則第七部分
- My Lord. - Part Seven, Code of Conduct.
請記住在本案中  你是證人
Please try and remember that you are a witness
不是律師  伯頓先生
and not counsel in this case, Mr Burton.
法官閣下  我完全能感受到
My Lord, I am fully aware of the tragic circumstances
此時此地的悲慘氛圍
we have surrounding us
我完全能體會到伯頓先生的巨大痛苦
and I am keenly aware of Mr Burton's incomprehensible loss,
但在本案中
but in the case we have before us,
只有不回避伯頓先生的不幸
Mr Burton's distress cannot be avoided
才能保證我的委托人得到公平的審判
if my client is to be given a fair trial.
好吧
Very well then.
當你看見花園里的人時
When you saw the man in the garden,
是否正承受著某方面的壓力
were you under stress in any way?
-是  -請你解釋何為律師標準投訴
- Yes. - What is a Bar Standards complaint?
是一種投訴出庭律師的
It's a formal letter listing a complaint
正式信函
against a practising barrister.
你是否收到過這樣的投訴
Have you ever received such a complaint?
有
I have.
能告訴我們是誰投訴你嗎
Can you tell us who wrote that complaint?
-我曾經的一個委托人  -請說出他的名字
- A former client of mine wrote it. - His name, please?
利亞姆·福伊爾
Liam Foyle.
房間很黑  你發現妻子倒在血泊里
In a dark room, in the shock and trauma of finding your wife
你在震驚和悲傷之中
in a pool of blood on the floor,
把她抱在懷里  當時還不知道兒子在哪里
holding her in your arms, still unclear as to where your son was,
你看向窗外  看到一個男人
you look up at the window and you see a man,
此人最近出于某種原因
a man who recently had been given cause
針對你的行為  向律師標準委員會
to make a serious complaint against your conduct
提起了措辭嚴厲的投訴
to the Bar Standards Board,
如果此人消失  則對你非常有利
a man whose absence from your life would be very useful indeed.
但并不是他  對嗎  伯頓先生
But it wasn't that man, was it, Mr Burton?
只是你希望是他
You just wanted it to be.
下集預告
-你必須阻止她  -現在有點晚了
- You have to Stop her. - A bit late for that.
她扭曲事實  顛倒黑白
She's twisting the facts to make them wrong.
她的工作做得不錯
Doing a good job of it too.
如果辯護有問題
If Defence had a problem,
當時就應該辯論
they should've argued it at the time.
問題才剛剛暴露出來
The issue has just come to light.
這是強有力的證據
There's compelling evidence!
我今晚可以過來嗎  我嚇壞了
Can I come round tonight, please? I'm freaking out.
他怎么知道  他不該知道的
How did he know? There's no way he could have known.
你殺她時  她是不是很快就死了
When you killed her, did she die quickly?
你如何忍受下去
How do you live with yourself?
-你讓我們都擔心了  -我只是太驚訝了
- You had us all worried for a minute. - I'm just full of surprises.
shad2脫 罪 大 師
第一季  第二集
YYeTs人人影視英劇社傾情奉獻
bei1翻譯  DT的寵物熊貓  愛卿遛小鳥
bei1翻譯  Silmar  噎死青春
bei1翻譯  死跑龍套的  面條打包子
bei1翻譯  妄想的絨布熊  蜂蜜檸檬  泰斯
bei1時間軸  吉吉  今  獄
bei1特別鳴謝  POTO的小飯桶
bei1特效&后期   sweet寶寶88
bei1總監   泰斯·雪諾
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新請登陸www.YYeTs.com